<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on andrelop.org</title>
    <link>http://andrelop.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on andrelop.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 21:18:08 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://andrelop.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Testing Hugo VSCode Plugins</title>
      <link>http://andrelop.org/posts/testing-hugo-vscode-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 21:18:08 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://andrelop.org/posts/testing-hugo-vscode-plugins/</guid>
      <description>Testing Hugo VSCode Plugins I&amp;rsquo;m testing VSCode plugins for Hugo, which is the static site generator solution I&amp;rsquo;m currently using.
At first, I have no interest in plugins to help with syntax highlight or code completion. The only thing I need is a set of shortcuts for running some Hugo commands, like starting and stopping the Hugo server, building the site, creating new posts, etc.
A plugin I found which does all of this is GoHugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update</title>
      <link>http://andrelop.org/posts/update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 18:08:02 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://andrelop.org/posts/update/</guid>
      <description>Personal Update What am I up to ? Well, I&amp;rsquo;m still working but these days I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly doing the same kind of work I used to do back in the day.
It took me many years to actually manage to distance myself from the most manual work. It&amp;rsquo;s still manual in the sense that my main work tool is a keyboard and I type at it the whole day, but I digress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>http://andrelop.org/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 17:35:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://andrelop.org/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>First Post This is yet another attempt to create a personal website. This time it&amp;rsquo;s made using Hugo and hosted on GitHub Pages.
I write the posts locally using some text editor (currently I use VS Code), check if they are OK running hugo server and if so, I just commit the posts to a GitHub repository.
This triggers a Git Hub Actions pipeline which actually builds and deploys the website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
